<resources>
    <string name="application_name">Money Quotient</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">455701804812980</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb455701804812980</string>
    <string name="terms">I agree to the </string>
    <string name="terms1"><u>terms &amp; condition</u> </string>
    <string name="forgotPassword"><u>Forgot Password ?</u></string>
    <string name="terms_condition">Money Quotient Website viz..www.moneyquotient.in and Mobile Application including but not limited to "Money quotient and  MQ ” (hereinafter referred as "Mobile App") is owned and maintained by “Satyaman Consultancy” (hereinafter referred as the  "Company"). By accessing, using and/or registering on the Website/ Mobile App you have read, understood and agreed to be legally bound by the terms of this disclaimer, the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions governing this Website/ Mobile App (collectively, "the Governing Conditions"). The Company reserves the right to make changes to the Website/ Mobile App and the Governing Conditions at any time.


Your usage of the Website/Mobile App, is entirely at your own risk. If you do not agree with any of the Governing Conditions, you should discontinue usage of the Website/Mobile App and/or Services and Information. Your continued use of the Website/ Mobile App shall mean your deemed acceptance to the Governing Conditions, as modified from time to time.


The Company provides information and services on the Website / Mobile App in the form of articles, statements, financial information, statement of accounts, presentations (collectively, "the Services and Information"). The Company obtains some of the said Services and Information from third party sources.  Some of the said information may also be delayed and may not be accurate. The Company makes no representation, warranty or guarantee as to the quality, accuracy, completeness of the Services and Information provided on or through the Website/ Mobile App. The Company makes no representations, warranties or guarantees (express or implied) that the contents of the Website/Mobile App or Services and Information are free from infection by viruses or other code or computer programming or anything else which has contaminating or destructive properties; and shall have no liability in respect thereof. Any of the Services and Information may be prone to shortcomings, defects or inaccuracies due to technical reasons.


The Services and Information do not constitute investment or financial advice or tax advice or any advise to trade in securities and expert opinion in this regard may be taken.


The Services and Information are dependent on information received from third party sources and other factors and may not be accurate or suitable for all categories of users and users are advised to take expert opinion and exercise discretion in making investment decisions and the Company is in no way involved in either advising or taking decisions. The Company is in no way liable for any action taken based on the Information and Services.


The Company is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of the Website/Mobile App or Services and Information.


The Company disclaims all liability of whatever nature, to any user, on account of the use of the Website/Mobile App or Services and Information. In no event shall the Company or its affiliates or its group company or its employees, directors or authorized representatives be held liable for any direct, indirect, special, consequential, punitive or exemplary damages of any nature whatsoever, for any decision made or action taken in reliance upon the Services and Information.


The Company/its employees/authorized representatives will not be responsible for any liability in respect of any person/entity directly or indirectly suffering any consequential losses, damages or claims of whatever nature as a result of any shortcoming, defect or inaccuracy that may have crept in on this Website/Mobile Application, or otherwise using the information available on this Website/Mobile App in any manner.


Part of this Website/Mobile App may contain advertising and other material submitted by third parties / users and the Company does not accept liability in respect of any such materials / advertisements and will not be responsible for any errors, omissions. Any third party links which are made available are not under the control of the Company and the Company is not liable or responsible for the same.


Where certain Services and Information are based on Short Messaging System (SMS), the same shall be subject to the TRAI regulations and also to your telecom service provider, as may be applicable from time to time. The Company cannot be held responsible for non-delivery or delay in delivery of SMS to your mobile phone/handset.


The Company reserves the right to deny access of the Website/Mobile App or Service and Information to anyone, at its sole discretion.


The usage of the Website/Mobile App is exclusively subject to the laws of India and the jurisdiction of the courts of Chennai in India.  The Company expressly disclaims any implied warranties or liabilities imputed by the laws of any other jurisdiction. This Website/Mobile App is specifically for users in the territory of India, though access to users outside India is not specifically denied.
</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">This Privacy Policy sets forth the reasonable security practices and procedures adopted by ”Satyaman Consultancy” (hereinafter referred as the “Company”) and shall apply to the use and disclosure and sharing of sensitive personal data or information (“Personal Information”) provided by the registered users of the website www.moneyquotient.in  and Mobile App (hereinafter referred as Mobile App), which is owned and operated   by the Company.\n\n
This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time and shall be deemed to be incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use of the Website/ Mobile App.\n\n
<b>1. Collection of information</b>\n\n
The Mobile App would require registration, and you are required to provide your details such as an email address, a password and other information. In some cases, you will also be required to provide your Name, PAN, Bank Account Number [“KYC information”] at the time of registration /activation of such facility.\n\n
From time to time, the Website/Mobile App may also request other Personal Information to provide you with other benefits of the Services. On all such occasions, you will have the opportunity to provide or to decline to provide that Personal Information.\n\n
<b>2. Use of personal information</b>\n\n
The Website/ Mobile App uses and discloses your Personal Information only as follows:\n\n
• To full fill / complete your requests for products and services offered, or subscribed or availed by you on the Website/Mobile App.\n
• To deliver to you any notices, alerts, advice, notifications and communications relevant to your use of the Services.\n
• To analyse Website/Mobile App usage and improve the services offered.\n
• For market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity.\n
• To Third Party Service Providers that provide services to the Company and are bound by these same privacy restrictions.\n
• To improve features, tailor the Website/Mobile App to your interests, and to get in touch with you whenever necessary.\n
For any of these purposes, we may use group companies / affiliates, third party vendors, agents, contractors, consultants or service providers (individually a ‘Third Party Service Provider’ and collectively, the “Third Party Service Providers”) We may also use them to help us in providing the features of the Website/Mobile App, such as sending email messages on our behalf, collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting you regarding any problem with such Services or hosting and operating a particular feature or functionality. Such Third Party Service Providers are bound by privacy restrictions which are similar to the restrictions mentioned in this Policy.\n\n
<b>3. Sharing and disclosure of personal information</b>\n\n
We will not sale, share, rent or trade your Personal Information with any affiliated or unaffiliated third parties. Further, we will also not disclose your Personal Information with any affiliated or unaffiliated third parties, except as mentioned above and also to: Provide you the product and services transaction processing and report generation\n
•	Confirm with any legal requirements or comply with legal process \n
•	Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services\n
•	Protect the interests of the Company, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents, or of other persons\n\n
<b>4.Promotional communication</b>\n\n
From  the Website/ Mobile App\n
The Website would provide you with periodic summaries of your Account Information and send email / SMS alerts. The Website/Mobile App also allows you to subscribe to email newsletters, research information, notifications and from time to time may transmit emails / SMS promoting the Website/Mobile App or third-party products or services. You have the ability to opt-out of receiving our promotional emails / SMS, notification and to terminate your newsletter subscriptions or notification facility as the case may be by following the instructions on the Website/Mobile App. Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of service-related emails / SMS - such transactional alerts.\n
In case you participate in surveys and contests any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy, except as specifically set forth in the rules for those surveys.\n\n
<b>5. Third party services and websites</b>\n\n
The Company shall not be responsible for any actions or policies of third party website, and you should check the applicable privacy policy of such third party when providing personally identifiable information to any third party websites.\n\n
<b>6.Use of cookies and online session information</b>\n\n
The Website will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies" sent to your browser from a web server or other means. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive.\n
The Website/Mobile App uses cookies for  improving our services and providing you with the full functionality of our services.\n\n
<b>7. Security of your data</b>\n\n
When you register for the Services, the Website/Mobile App requires a Login ID and a password from you for your privacy and security. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Login ID and password and you may not provide these credentials to any third party. We recommend that you change your password periodically.\n
Your password must be in line with the specifications of our Website and the Company will not be responsible for any wrongful use / misuse of your User ID / Log In ID / Password of your account by a third party.\n
While accessing your personal financial information (which we may provide through a third party source), the Website/Mobile App use appropriate security / firewall / encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session, and to protect Website/ Mobile App accounts and systems from unauthorized access. Suitable encryption techniques are adopted to ensure that even we do not have access to your password.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Money Quotient</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Money Quotient</string>
    <string name="ques1">1. What is your age?</string>
    <string name="ques2">2. What do you expect to be your next major expenditure?</string>
    <string name="ques3">3. When do you expect to use most of the money you are now accumulating in your investments?</string>
    <string name="ques4">4. Over the next several years, you expect your annual income to:</string>
    <string name="ques5">5. Due to a general market correction, one of your investments loses 14% of its value a short time after you buy it. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="ques6">6. Which of these investing plans would you choose for your investment rupees?</string>
    <string name="ques7">7. Assuming you are investing in a stock, which one do you choose?</string>
    <string name="ques8">8. Assuming you are investing in only one bond, which bond do you choose?</string>
    <string name="ques9">9. You expect inflation to return and it has been suggested that you invest in \'hard\' assets, which have historically outpaced inflation. Your only financial assets are long-term bonds. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="ques10">10. You have just reached the $10,000 plateau on a TV game show. Now you must choose between quitting with the $10,000 in hand or betting the entire $10,000 in one of three alternative scenarios. Which do you choose?</string>


</resources>
